const dayEightQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "… is a Hadith that is reported by an unreliable reporter and containing vulgar statements that are against what a reliable reporter narrates.",
    options: [
      "Al Hadith ‘Aziz",
      "Al Mawdu’",
      "Al Mudraj",
      "Al Munkar",
      "Al Gareeb",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Al-Mudraj is classified into two, what are they?",
    options: [
      "Mudrajus Sabiqah and Mudraju lahiqah",
      "Mudrajus Shadh and Mudrajul Gareeb",
      "Mudrajus Sanad and Mudrajul Matn",
      "Mudrajus Sahih and Mudrajul Da’eef",
      "Mudrajus Snad and Mudrajus Shuyuk",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Is it all Musnad (Supported) Hadith that are authentic?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "… is a Hadith narrated by a more reliable reporter against what a lesser authority reported.",
    options: [
      "Alhadithul Mahfuz",
      "Alhadithus Shadh",
      "Alhadithul Munkar",
      "Alhadithul Ma’ruf",
      "Alhadithul Mashur",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "A Muslim that meets Companion(s) of the Prophet (May the peace and blessing of Allaah be upon him) and died as a Muslim is known as …",
    options: ["Tabi’y", "Sahabah", "Sahabiyah", "Sharif", "Maolah"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Who among the Companions reported Hadith the most?",
    options: [
      "Abubakr Sidiq",
      "‘Aisha bint Abubakr",
      "Ali bn Abi Talib",
      "Abu Hurairah",
      "Anas bn Malik",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which book is the first book of authentic Hadiths?",
    options: [
      "As Saheehah by Albani",
      "Sahih al-Bukhari",
      "Sahih Muslim",
      "Muwata by Imam Malik",
      "Almaodu’at by Ibn Jaoziy",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "………………………is a Hadith which is narrated by a large number of its reporters equally at the beginning, at the middle and at the end, reported from a large number of people that they cannot be expected to agree upon a lie, all of them together.",
    options: [
      "Al Ma’ruf",
      "Al Mutawatir",
      "Al Mashur",
      "Al Marfu’",
      "Al Mahfuz",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "…………………….is a Hadith that was narrated by a reliable reporter against what an unreliable reporter narrates.",
    options: ["Al Mahfuz", "As Shadh", "Al Munkar", "Al Ma’ruf", "Al Mashur"],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Is ‘Aziz’ (Rare) a condition for an authentic Hadith?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "………………………is a Hadith that is void of a condition out of conditions of Hadith ‘Hassan’ (Good)",
    options: [
      "Al Maqlub",
      "Ad Da’eef",
      "Al Mu’allal",
      "Al Munkar",
      "Al Mahfuz",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "……………………..is a Hadith which was reported by more than two reporters equally at each stage of Isnad and did not reach the level of Mutawatir.",
    options: [
      "Al Ma’ruf",
      "Al Mudtarib",
      "Al Mashur",
      "Al Marfu’",
      "Al Mahfuz",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "……………………..is a Hadith that its defect is that there is an overturn in the arrangement of chains and content.",
    options: [
      "Al Maqlub",
      "Ad Da’eef",
      "Al Mu’allal",
      "Al Munkar",
      "Al Mahfuz",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "………………………is the narration from Successors or those who follow them.",
    options: [
      "Al Hadith ‘Aziz",
      "Al Maoquf",
      "Al Mudraj",
      "Al Munqati’",
      "Al Maqtu’",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "……………………….is the narration that conceals defects while it shows authenticity from mere looking.",
    options: [
      "Al Maqlub",
      "Ad Da’eef",
      "Al Mu’allal",
      "Al Munkar",
      "Al Mahfuz",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
];
export default dayEightQuestions;
